<?xml version="1.0"?>
<ArrayOfCircle xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <Circle>
    <Name>DjangoRest</Name>
    <x>60.88123268698061</x>
    <y>49.956717451523545</y>
    <Website>www.djangoproject.com</Website>
    <Description>Django is a free and open source web application framework, written in Python. A web framework is a set of components that helps you to develop websites faster and easier.</Description>
  </Circle>
  <Circle>
    <Name>Workday</Name>
    <x>35.855263157894733</x>
    <y>46.21710526315789</y>
    <Website>www.workday.com</Website>
    <Description>Workday, Inc. is an on‑demand (cloud-based) financial management and human capital management software vendor. It was founded by David Duffield, the founder and former CEO of the ERP giant PeopleSoft, and former PeopleSoft chief strategist Aneel Bhusri following Oracle's hostile takeover of PeopleSoft in 2005.</Description>
  </Circle>
  <Circle>
    <Name>Angular</Name>
    <x>57.284452908587255</x>
    <y>6.85595567867036</y>
    <Website>www.angularjs.org</Website>
    <Description>AngularJS is a structural framework for dynamic web apps. It lets you use HTML as your template language and lets you extend HTML's syntax to express your application's components clearly and succinctly. Angular's data binding and dependency injection eliminate much of the code you would otherwise have to write.</Description>
  </Circle>
  <Circle>
    <Name>NothingToSeeHere</Name>
    <x>6.3435345161251906</x>
    <y>33.669962534090367</y>
    <Website>www.google.com</Website>
    <Description>A fix to something that is broken</Description>
  </Circle>
  <Circle>
    <Name>Pair_Programming</Name>
    <x>29.228704986149584</x>
    <y>21.913954293628809</y>
    <Website>www.pairprogramming.com</Website>
    <Description>Pair programming (sometimes referred to as peer programming) is an agile software development technique in which two programmers work as a pair together on one workstation. One, the driver, writes code while the other, the observer, pointer or navigator, reviews each line of code as it is typed in.</Description>
  </Circle>
  <Circle>
    <Name>Biztalk</Name>
    <x>37.01523545706371</x>
    <y>10.513331024930748</y>
    <Website>www.msdn.com</Website>
    <Description>BizTalk is an industry initiative headed by Microsoft to promote Extensible Markup Language (XML) as the common data exchange language for e-commerce and application integration on the Internet. While not a standards body per se, the group is fostering a common XML message-passing architecture to tie systems together.</Description>
  </Circle>
  <Circle>
    <Name>EmberJS</Name>
    <x>20.987707756232687</x>
    <y>35.128116343490305</y>
    <Website>www.emberjs.com</Website>
    <Description>emberjs.com. Free software portal. Ember.js is an open-source JavaScript application framework, based on the model-view-controller (MVC) pattern. It allows developers to create scalable single-page web applications by incorporating common idioms and best practices into the framework.</Description>
  </Circle>
  <Circle>
    <Name>DotNET</Name>
    <x>13.434903047091412</x>
    <y>11.422264542936288</y>
    <Website>www.microsoft.com</Website>
    <Description>.NET Framework (pronounced dot net) is a software framework developed by Microsoft that runs primarily on Microsoft Windows.</Description>
  </Circle>
  <Circle>
    <Name>Java</Name>
    <x>4.388850415512465</x>
    <y>18.680747922437675</y>
    <Website>www.java.com</Website>
    <Description>Java is a programming language expressly designed for use in the distributed environment of the Internet. It was designed to have the "look and feel" of the C++ language, but it is simpler to use than C++ and enforces an object-oriented programming model.</Description>
  </Circle>
  <Circle>
    <Name>VisualStudio_2015</Name>
    <x>17.564058171745152</x>
    <y>4.3022853185595569</y>
    <Website>www.visualstudio.com</Website>
    <Description>Microsoft Visual Studio is an integrated development environment (IDE) from Microsoft. It is used to develop computer programs for Microsoft Windows, as well as web sites, web applications and web services.</Description>
  </Circle>
</ArrayOfCircle>